<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
    <title>The City Has Pulled The Wool Over Our Eyes But No Longer!</title>
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/atom.xml"/>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info"/>
    <generator uri="https://www.getzola.org/">Zola</generator>
    <updated>2024-04-17T12:44:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/atom.xml</id>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Missing Are Not Missing—They’ve Been Taken</title>
        <published>2024-04-17T12:44:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-17T12:44:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/missing-not-missing/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/missing-not-missing/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/missing-not-missing/">&lt;p&gt;Something is happening in the city. Something no one wants to talk about.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The numbers don’t lie, even if the officials do. People are vanishing. Not just a few. Not just here and there. &lt;strong&gt;Hundreds&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. And not the kind of people who get press coverage. Not the kind who have families that can afford billboards and search parties.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s the unhoused. The forgotten. The “undesirables.”&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’re disappearing from shelters, from alleyways, from beneath overpasses and abandoned buildings. One day they’re there, the next they’re gone. No bodies. No witnesses. No investigations. Just silence.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve spoken to volunteers, street medics, even a few ex-cops who still have a conscience. They all say the same thing: &lt;strong&gt;the city is pretending nothing’s wrong&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But something is very wrong.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe they’re being taken. Not by gangs. Not by cults. Not even by the Mole People. No—this is bigger. This is &lt;strong&gt;off-world&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliens.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know how that sounds. I know what you’re thinking. But I’m not talking about little green men or flying saucers. I’m talking about &lt;strong&gt;interdimensional entities&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;—beings who don’t travel in ships, but in folds of space. Beings who don’t speak, but resonate.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’ve come here for one reason: &lt;strong&gt;magic&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our planet’s arcane field is unique. It’s volatile, layered, and deeply entangled with biology. The aliens—who I believe originate from a realm called &lt;strong&gt;Kirellion&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;—don’t have magic like ours. Theirs is sterile, crystalline, mathematical. Ours is chaotic, emotional, alive.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They want to understand it. And they’re using our people to do it.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The missing aren’t dead. They’re &lt;strong&gt;test subjects&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. Taken to hidden labs—some underground, some in orbit, some in places that don’t exist on any map. They’re being exposed to raw ley energy, infused with sigils, broken and rebuilt.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And why? Because Kirellion is at war.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their enemy? &lt;strong&gt;Virex.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, the same Virex I’ve warned you about—the living archive drifting between dimensions, sending its Sentinels to extract knowledge and erase witnesses. Kirellion and Virex are locked in an arms race, and Earth is the battleground.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are the resource.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Pale? Just a symptom. The Mole People? Just collateral damage. The disappearances? &lt;strong&gt;Harvesting.&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you think this is just paranoia, ask yourself: why did the stars shift last week? Why did every bird in the city fly west at 3:17 AM? Why did the mayor’s emergency broadcast system activate for 0.7 seconds and then shut down?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They know.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And now, so do you.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Mole People Know What The Pale Is—And They’re Not Telling Us</title>
        <published>2024-04-16T02:24:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-16T02:24:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mole-people-pale/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mole-people-pale/</id>
        
        <content type="html" xml:base="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mole-people-pale/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking about the Mole People again. You remember them—those subterranean entities that emerged from beneath the city, not from the sewers, but from the ancient layers of earth that predate our maps, our buildings, even our understanding of what this planet is. They’re not rats. They’re not mutants. They’re something older. Something deliberate.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And lately? They’ve been quiet. Too quiet.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to track their movements—strange tremors, sudden sinkholes, the occasional claw mark on a subway wall. But for the past few weeks, it’s like they’ve vanished. Not gone, mind you. Just… hiding. Retreating. And I think I know why.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s The Pale.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since The Pale started circulating through the underworld, the Mole People have been pulling back. Abandoning their usual haunts. Avoiding the eastern tunnels. Even the old blood cults say the deep passages feel “wrong” now. Like something is leaking into them. Something that doesn’t belong.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is The Pale, really?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We know it’s not a normal drug. It’s milky, chalky, and cold to the touch. It doesn’t just affect the mind—it warps perception, memory, even biology. People who take it report visions, mutations, and encounters with entities that don’t exist in this plane. And yet, somehow, they remain lucid.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s the thing: I don’t think The Pale was made for us.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it was made for the Mole People. Or by them. Or maybe it’s something they were trying to &lt;strong&gt;contain&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a legend—buried in the footnotes of a banned anthropology journal—that speaks of a “White Curse” carried by the Deep Folk. A substance that was never meant to surface. A gift or a punishment from something they worship beneath the crust. They called it “The Breath of the Hollow Star.”&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sound familiar?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if The Pale is that curse? What if it’s leaking upward, not because someone is distributing it, but because the Mole People &lt;strong&gt;lost control of it&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or worse—what if they’re running from it?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve heard whispers that the eastern tunnels are no longer safe. That something is hunting down the Deep Folk. That their cities—yes, cities—beneath our feet are collapsing. Not from war. Not from decay. But from &lt;strong&gt;infestation&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And what if The Pale is the infestation?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if it’s not a drug at all, but a &lt;strong&gt;sentient substance&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;? A parasite. A messenger. Something that was buried for a reason and is now using us as vessels.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mole People know. They’ve always known. That’s why they’re silent. That’s why they’re retreating. That’s why they haven’t surfaced in weeks.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’re afraid.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if the Mole People are afraid, then we should be terrified.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because whatever The Pale is… it’s not done yet.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</content>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Shady Pines Incident: Killer Robots, Space Magic, and a Missing Mind</title>
        <published>2024-04-15T01:48:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-15T01:48:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/shady-pines-robots/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/shady-pines-robots/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;They’re calling it a gas leak. A tragic accident. Faulty wiring. A boiler malfunction. Pick your excuse. The official story keeps changing, like a bad improv troupe trying to cover up a murder. But I know what happened at Shady Pines. I’ve connected the dots.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>Something Is Crawling Into the City—And It’s Not Human</title>
        <published>2024-04-14T06:27:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-14T06:27:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/something-crawling/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/something-crawling/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;something-is-crawling-into-the-city-and-it-s-not-human&quot;&gt;Something Is Crawling Into the City—And It’s Not Human&lt;&#x2F;h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been watching the streets again. Listening. The usual noise is there—sirens, deals, threats, the hum of a city pretending it’s still in control. But beneath that? Something new. Something wrong.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Truth Is Far Worse: We Are Not Dealing With Rats—We Are Facing the Rise of the Mole People</title>
        <published>2024-04-14T02:37:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-14T02:37:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mole-people-invading/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mole-people-invading/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I need to correct a mistake. A grave mistake.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my last post, I told you all that mutant rats had emerged from the sewers, evolving past anything science or magic could explain. And while that post was based on the truth as I understood it then, I now realize how deeply misled I was. The creatures we saw that night were &lt;strong&gt;not rats at all&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. The glow, the sigils, the unnatural way they moved—they were &lt;strong&gt;something far worse&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were &lt;strong&gt;Mole People&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Sewer Rats Have Evolved—And The Corruption Is Spreading</title>
        <published>2024-04-12T03:15:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-12T03:15:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mutant-rats-sewers/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/mutant-rats-sewers/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;For years, I’ve warned about the strange mutations lurking beneath our cities. The sewers, packed with chemical runoff, discarded pharmaceuticals, and now—thanks to the greed of megacorporations—&lt;strong&gt;residual arcane energy&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;, have become the perfect breeding ground for creatures beyond natural comprehension. I’ve heard whispers, collected fragmented stories, but no one ever took them seriously. I never had undeniable proof.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until now.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>The Vanishing Bikers: Evidence of Men in Black Abductions</title>
        <published>2024-04-07T04:21:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-07T04:21:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/men-in-black-bikers/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/men-in-black-bikers/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;For years, the shadowy presence of the Men in Black has haunted the edges of our reality. They’ve been whispered about in hushed tones, feared by those who’ve encountered them, and dismissed by the ignorant. But now, a disturbing new pattern has emerged—one that cannot be ignored. Our nation’s bikers—those fearless road warriors who embrace the open highways—are disappearing. And the evidence is clear: the Men in Black are responsible.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
    <entry xml:lang="en">
        <title>No More Lies: This City Has Pulled the Wool Over Our Eyes for Too Long</title>
        <published>2024-04-06T05:18:00+00:00</published>
        <updated>2024-04-06T05:18:00+00:00</updated>
        
        <author>
          <name>
            
              John Doe
            
          </name>
        </author>
        
        <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/city-pulled-the-wool/"/>
        <id>https://thecityhaspulledthewooloveroureyesbutnolonger.info/posts/city-pulled-the-wool/</id>
        
        <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;For years, we’ve walked these streets, lived our lives, and assumed that everything around us was as it should be. We trusted the neon lights, the towering skyscrapers, the hum of the city as proof of stability, of normalcy. But I am here to tell you that &lt;strong&gt;nothing is normal about this city&lt;&#x2F;strong&gt;. Not anymore.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;</summary>
        
    </entry>
</feed>
